Jenelyn Pieloor

+63 962 745 8011 · devjenny.official@gmail.com · github.com/devJennyy Ayala, Zamboanga City, Zamboanga Del Sur, Philippines

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

A highly motivated and enthusiastic individual that focuses on web development with a strong passion in frontend development particularly in react/tailwind. I specialize in turning concepts into engaging web realities & crafting user-friendly interfaces that provide exceptional digital experiences.

TECH STACKS

HTML5 ReactJS Strapi
CSS TypeScript GraphQL
JavaScript Tailwind CSS Framer Motion
Git ShadCN

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Frontend Developer Part time Job

Apr 2024 - Sep 2024

- My role involves translating design wireframes into pixel perfect integration along with making it visually appealing and highly functional web pages. I also have worked with Strapi CMS and GraphQL for queries and API implementation.
- Played a key role in developing front-end solutions for a newer version of the system using ReactJS, TypeScript, and Tailwind CSS to create a more user-friendly and responsive interface. Additionally, utilized Framer Motion to implement smooth animations and transitions on several pages, enhancing the user experience.

UI/UX designer and Frontend Developer Freelance

Nov 2022 - May 2024

- Designed and developed multiple commission-based projects from scratch, crafting user interfaces in Figma and seamlessly translating them into responsive front-end solutions using ReactJS, TypeScript, and Tailwind CSS.
- Collaborated closely with clients to understand requirements and deliver customized solutions.
- Created various front-end solutions, including a Management System, Tracking System, Appointment System, and more.

WORKS AND PROJECTS

WMSU Center of Continuing Education Management System

I designed the user interface for a web application that manages WMSU CCE events. The
application allows users to create and update events, invite speakers, and send a QR
attendance feature via email. My focus was on delivering a smooth, intuitive user
experience.

Shop Online

I designed and developed a frontend e-commerce website made in ReactJS, TailwindCSS,
Typescript to create a modern online shopping experience. I integrated additional libraries
such as ShadCN for enhanced user interface components, aceternity for other features, and
EmblaCarousel for seamless product image carousels.

Finance App

• I developed a frontend for a proposed mobile finance application to help users effectively manage their finances. I focused on creating a user-friendly interface that allows users to visualize their finance.

Kawaii-Verse

 A proposed anime archive where it features popular and trending anime list along with top characters displayed in both list and grid views. I built the frontend using React with TypeScript and styled using Tailwind CSS, along with other frontend libraries such as Shadon/Aceternity to provide a more user-friendly experience.

JumpStart

• I developed the frontend for this web app that creates a management and tracking website that oversees commissions and helps users find commissioners along with ensuring an intuitive and user-friendly experience for both managing and tracking commissions.

Messaging App

 A fun project where I created a static messaging application featuring both dark and light modes.

Spotify Clone

• I re-created the Spotify UI for fun as a practice project, focusing on replicating the design and layout of the original application.

EDUCATION & CERTIFICATIONS

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science

Western Mindanao State University 2019 - 2023

Senior High School

ICT - Information Communication and Technology

AWARDS

Curricular Achiever (1.75 GWA)

College of Computing Studies Western Mindanao State University

3rd Best Research Paper

Thesis Project Western Mindanao State University